//object array of questions. The trivia game will pull from this object array.
var questions = [{
    question: "Who caught the helmet catch for the Giants in Super Bowl XLII?",
    answer1: "Victor Cruz",
    answer2: "David Tyree",
    answer3: "Mario Manningham",
    answer4: "Plaxico Burress",
    correct: "David Tyree",
  },

  {
    question: "What running back retired from the Giants in the prime of his career?",
    answer1: "Brandon Jacobs",
    answer2: "Ron Dayne",
    answer3: "Tiki Barber",
    answer4: "Rodney Hampton",
    correct: "Tiki Barber",

  },

  {
    question: " Who was the starting QB for the Giants in 1994?",
    answer1: "Phil Simms",
    answer2: "Danny Kannell",
    answer3: "Dave Brown",
    answer4: "Kerry Collins",
    correct: "Dave Brown",

  },

  {
    question: " Who was the qb of the Giants in Superbowl XXV?",
    answer1: "Jeff Hostetler",
    answer2: "Phil Simms",
    answer3: "Kerry Collins",
    answer4: "Eli Manning",
    correct: "Jeff Hostetler",
  },

  {
    question: "What Giants linebacker changed the game of football?",
    answer1: "Harry Carson",
    answer2: "Lawrence Taylor",
    answer3: "Carl Banks",
    answer4: "Antonio Pierce",
    correct: "Lawrence Taylor",
  },

  {
    question: "What Giants receiver proposed to a kicking net?",
    answer1: "Amani Toomer",
    answer2: "Odell Beckham Jr.",
    answer3: "Steve Smith",
    answer4: "victor Cruz",
    correct: "Odell Beckham Jr.",
  },

  {
    question: "What Giants player was highly successful as an offensive and defensive player?",
    answer1: "Y.A. Tittle",
    answer2: "Sam Huff",
    answer3: "Frank Gifford",
    answer4: "Pepper Johnson",
    correct: "Frank Gifford",
  },

  {
    question: "what year did the Giants stop playing at the Polo Grounds ?",
    answer1: "1948",
    answer2: "1955",
    answer3: "1962",
    answer4: "1959",
    correct: "1955",
  },

  {
    question: "what year did the Giants play at the Yale Bowl?",
    answer1: "1968",
    answer2: "1978",
    answer3: "1974",
    answer4: "1994",
    correct: "1974",
  },

  {
    question: "what head coach has the most wins in the Giants franchise history?",
    answer1: "Tom Coughlin",
    answer2: "Jim Fassell",
    answer3: "Bill Parcells",
    answer4: "Steve Owen",
    correct: "Steve Owen",
  },

  {
    question: "what former Giants player won Dancing with the stars?",
    answer1: "Michael Strahan",
    answer2: "Rashad Jennings",
    answer3: "Antonio Pierce",
    answer4: "Ahmad Bradshaw",
    correct: "Rashad Jennings",
  }
]
